{
    "id": "eb6daac221e64db9ab63e7788aca332d",
    "title": "Singular and plural nouns",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "1d87f733c51f47e38b6ff486e594cae8",
            "title": "Singular And Plural Nouns",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He weighs nine ……………………….",
                    "description": "When the word score is used after a numeral, it does not have the plural form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "stone",
                        "stones",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "That car cost me five ……………………… dollars.",
                    "description": "When numerals like hundred and thousand are used after another numeral, they do not have the plural form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "thousand",
                        "thousands"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I bought three ……………………… oranges.",
                    "description": "When dozen is used after a numeral, it does not have a plural form.",
                    "answers": [
                        "dozen",
                        "dozens"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "India won by …………………………. and three runs.",
                    "description": "The noun innings is always used in the singular.",
                    "answers": [
                        "innings",
                        "an inning",
                        "an innings"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "His ………………………… small but he has no debt.",
                    "description": "When means has the meaning of wealth, it is used in the plural.",
                    "answers": [
                        "mean is",
                        "means is",
                        "means are"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………………….. not only destroy our property but also carry disease.",
                    "description": "The collective noun vermin is singular in form but it is always used as a plural noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Vermin",
                        "Vermins"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The ………………………….. needs repairs.",
                    "description": "The possessive case is chiefly used with the names of living things.",
                    "answers": [
                        "house roof",
                        "house's roof",
                        "roof of the house"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has no ……………………….. for his parents.",
                    "description": "Respect means regard respects means compliments.",
                    "answers": [
                        "respect",
                        "respects"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Both countries have withdrawn their ………………………..",
                    "description": "Force means strength forces means troops.",
                    "answers": [
                        "force",
                        "forces"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Why are you always putting on ……………………….?",
                    "description": "Airs can mean affected manners.",
                    "answers": [
                        "air",
                        "airs"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We must all stand up for the common ……………………",
                    "description": "The common good means the interests of all.",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "goods"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He wouldn’t listen to my ………………………",
                    "description": "Advice means counsel advices can mean information.",
                    "answers": [
                        "advice",
                        "advices",
                        "advise"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}